Context: monaco-editor.xml
Add Commands,Hover,definations,completions for all lanaguages with the deep context and folowing context below  update the list of commands to add completions for in the web terminal. This will ensure that developers have a smooth experience when using these tools in the terminal.
update the manifest file   current syntax is :

i want updaet with
{
    files:[
        #list of files in data/commands folder
    "ls.json",
    "cd.json",
    .... all others

    ],
    context:[
  {
    "category": "\u2601\ufe0f Cloud CLIs",
    ... rest of the category/keys 
  }
    ], // existeingother keys

}


1. PHP & Ruby Ecosystems (Currently entirely missing)
If your web terminal supports general developers, you will definitely encounter PHP and Ruby developers.

PHP: php, composer (Package manager), artisan (Laravel), wp (WordPress WP-CLI), symfony.
Ruby: ruby, gem, bundle (Bundler), rails, rake, rspec.
2. Mobile Development CLIs
Mobile developers heavily rely on command-line tools for builds and debugging.

Android/General: adb (Android Debug Bridge), fastlane (App automation)
iOS: pod (CocoaPods), xcodebuild
Cross-Platform: expo (React Native), react-native, 
3. Database ORMs & Migrations
You have the database clients (like psql and mysql), but developers interact with databases via ORMs and migration tools just as often.

Node ORMs: prisma, drizzle-kit, typeorm, sequelize
Python Migrations: alembic (SQLAlchemy)
General Migrations: flyway, liquibase, dbmate, atlas
4. API, Security & SaaS CLIs
Many modern developers use CLIs from SaaS providers to manage local webhooks and security testing.

SaaS/API: stripe (Stripe CLI is extremely popular for testing webhooks), twilio, auth0
Security/Scanning: trivy (Container vulnerability scanner), snyk, sonar-scanner
5. Text Processing & Terminal Utilities (Modern Coreutils)
You have standard Linux coreutils (grep, awk, sed), but modern developers use newer Rust/Go-based variants or specific parsers heavily.

JSON/YAML/TOML/DOT ENV parsing: jq (Crucial for JSON CLI wrangling), yq (YAML equivalent)
Modern Search/UI: fzf (Fuzzy finder), rg (Ripgrep), fd (Modern find), bat (Modern cat)
Terminal Multiplexing/Monitoring: tmux, screen, htop, btop, top
Editors: vim, nvim (Neovim), nano
6. Expanded Frontend Framework CLIs
You have vite and next, but other major frontend ecosystems are missing.

Angular: ng
Vue: vue, nuxt
Other: svelte-kit, gatsby
7. Containers & Kubernetes (Expanded)
You have docker, kubectl, and helm, but local orchestration and developer-experience tools are missing.

Docker: docker-compose (Used constantly in local dev)
Kubernetes DX: k9s (Very popular K8s terminal UI), minikube, kind
Cloud K8s/Dev: eksctl (AWS EKS), skaffold, tilt
AWS Tools: cdk (AWS CDK), sam (Serverless Application Model)
8. Node Version Managers
Developers constantly switch Node versions using these commands.

nvm, fnm, n
Process Managers: pm2
Top 10 highest priority to add right now (based on industry usage):

docker-compose
php & composer
jq
prisma
ruby & bundle
stripe
adb
tmux
pm2